Sujay Mahadik



mahadik203@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/sujay-mahadik



+91 9004133463



https://www.sujaymahadik.website

Summary

I am often found juggling with interests that include coding, graphic design, all the way to appreciating good coffee and nerding out over pop fiction, astrophysics and dystopian literature. I have 4 years of experience in full stack front end development, illustrations, graphics and motion design.

Co-Founded a remote, non-conforming design collective based in Paris focused on creating visual identity. Our collective has experience in diverse fields such as design, photography, UI/UX design among a few.

Working with Barclays around Enterprise and Data Integration Infrastructure Administration and Automation. ETL tools include Informatica and Ab Initio

Pursuing Masters in Economics from Ferguson College under Pune Uni's Open Learning Program

Experience



Service Delivery Analyst

Barclays

Apr 2021 - Present (2 months +)

Working with Barclays around Enterprise and Data Integration Infrastructure Administration and Automation.

ETL tools:

- Informatica
- Ab Initio

Co-Founder and Designer

The Jellyfish Collective

Jun 2020 - Present (1 year +)

The collective specializes in branding, visual identity and helping startups create design-based systems. Jellyfish was built on the notion of restoring balance to the relationship between designers and collaborators and create long-term partnerships.



Graduate Analyst

Barclays

Aug 2019 - Apr 2021 (1 year 9 months)

Barclays Global Service Centre (BGSC), India is a global capability center, supporting Barclays businesses worldwide, delivering innovative end-to-end business solutions in Technology, Operations and Functions.

Co-Founder and Designer

Infin8y Labs

Sep 2016 - May 2020 (3 years 9 months)

A hobby venture revolving around the idea for designing and manufacturing stationary and wearable accessories - posters, bookmarks, notebooks, calendars, pin-badges, t-shirts and more. Designing and Production were my primary responsibilities.

Project Intern

Persistent Systems

Sep 2017 - Jun 2018 (10 months)

Aim of the project was to create an Autonomous Drone and was done in a group of 6 students. The project involved working with cutting edge hardware technology.

I was looking after the simulation and designing terrains in Unity 3D Game Engine

Design and Technical Head

MIT CREON

Aug 2016 - Feb 2018 (1 year 7 months)

Web Development and Digital Marketing for MIT CREON 17, MIT CREON 18 along with graphic design for publicity boards and posters. The project also included an SMTP server ticket booking platform for an event.

Education

👸 Fergusson College

Master of Arts - MA, Economics

2019 - 2021

Savitribai Phule Pune University - School of Open learning

Part I Major Subjects - Public Economics, International Trade & Finance

Savitribai Phule Pune University

Bachelor of Engineering (BE), Information Technology

2015 - 2019

MIT College of Engineering

Top 3% in Department

Pace Junior Science College

HSC, Science

2013 - 2015

Among Top 1%, Awarded research scholarship

National English School, ICSE

ICSE

Licenses & Certifications

Blockchain Basics by University of Buffalo & The State University of New York Coursera

T682MSQWQARE

Smart Contracts by University at Buffalo & The State University of New York Coursera
GXN2XRK95XUT

- Internet Connection Cisco Networking Academy
 LTKPEEDADCK4
- Network Protocols and Architecture Cisco Networking Academy
 8ALZDM48SYWG
- The Data Scientist's Toolbox by Johns Hopkins University Coursera
 TPW5HGAGFFE9
- Textual Elements of Design: Fonts, Typography, and Spacing by University of Colorado Boulder Coursera

76XEHZZWN3GY

- Print and Digital Elements of Design: Branding and User Experience by University of Colorado Boulder Coursera

 YP9CNVY3NPF9
- Introduction to Philosophy by The University of Edinburgh Coursera
 M6SQT8L2KABN
- AWS Fundamentals: Going Cloud-Native Coursera EDSRWJK4FWTX
- The Data Science of Economics, Banking, and Finance, with Barton Poulson LinkedIn

Skills

Graphic Design • Adobe Illustrator • Python (Programming Language) • Ab Initio • Web Development • Visual Design • Data Analysis • Economic Data Analysis • Automation

Honors & Awards

Scholarship for Higher Education, Top 1% in Boards - Maharashtra State Board of Secondary and Higher Education Society

Mar 2015

- Primary School Scholarship
- International Olympiad of Mathematics 2008